Hakan Gundogdu

Frontend Developer

hakangundogdu.com

in http://linkedin.com/in/hakangundogdu1

https://github.com/hakangundogdu

Izmir, Turkey (GMT+3)

+90-532-621-7091

hakan.gundogdu@gmail.com

An enthusiastic React Frontend Developer with 2+ years of experience. Possesses strong problemsolving skills, analytical and methodical thinking, transferred from finance and graphic design background. Able to work at all stages of a project life cycle. Self-motivated person with the ability to work to the highest ethical standards. Proven to work both independently and within a team. Adaptive and fast-learner of new technologies and business requirements. Effective communicator with coworkers, and project/business partners.

Areas of Expertise

- React
- Typescript
- Javascrit ES6

- Redux
- NextJS
- TailwindCSS

- HTML/CSS
- Finance / Fintech
- Git

Experience

Upwork, Turkey, 01/2019 - Now

Software Engineer, Top-Rated-Plus Freelancer

- Worked with +200 clients.
- Designed and developed engaging webpages and web applications.
- Designed Pitch Decks and other marketing documents.
- Some of my clients: Johnson & Johnson, Novartis, Glasswall, Protective, Gateone, Abilitie

React, Next JS, TypeScript, Tailwind, HTML, CSS, WordPress, Git, Jira, Figma, Adobe Software

Trounceflow, London, UK, 04/2019 – 08/2019

Analyst, https://wp.trounceflow.com/

- Managed Frontend of the product
- Analysed financial data and created reports and insights.

Jaascript, HTML, CSS

Other Experiences

Bayyurt Group, Financial Analyst, Turkey, 2018 – 2019

Turkish Treasury, Senior Associate, Advisor to Head of Treasury, Turkey, 2008 - 2016

Education & Credentials

BA, Bogazici University, Economics, 2007, Istanbul, Turkey

GMAT: 760 (99th percentile) **TOEFL: 106**